哦,…该死!
Oh, sh-- shit!
你很紧张。
You are, uh, nervous.
没关系。
It's okay.
我第一次见到你的时候，就对自己说"这个人知道自己想要什么"
When I first saw you, I said to myself,
"This is a man that knows what he wants."
他只是，呃，害怕。
He's just, uh, afraid.
我不是害怕，只是…我知道，我知道，…事情就是这样。
Well, I'm not afraid, it's just that I--
I know, I know, It-- it is just the way...
things are.
但男人必须付出代价才能得到他想要的。
But a man must pay to get what he wants.
嗯?
Hmm?
所以我们才在这里，对吧?
That is why... we're all here, yes?
是的。
Yeah.
去和她谈谈。
Go talk to her.
来吧。
Come on.
她很甜。
She's very sweet.
你会看到。
You'll see.
Beatriz!
你好。
Hola.
嗨。
Hi.
你想让我看看你画的是什么吗?
You wanna show me what you're drawing?
我宁愿不。
I'd rather not.
Beatriz,对吧?
It's Beatriz, right?
卧室。
Bedroom.
…听着,……我们为什么不先谈谈? Ah, li-- listen, why,
wh-- why don't we just talk first?
好吧?
Okay?
你不想把时间浪费在说话上。
You don't want to waste time with talking.
没关系。
It's okay.
……你多大了?
H-- how old are you?
你喜欢几岁?
How old do you like?
不，我不是这个意思。
No, that's not what I meant.
我只是想了解你，了解你是谁。
I just want to get to know you,
-你喜欢十三?-别这样，求你了!
g-- g-- get to know who you are.
- 12 ?——不。
- You like thirteen? - Come on, no, please!
- Twelve? - No.
该死!
Shit!
爸爸!爸爸!
Papa! Papa!
联邦调查局!马上把枪放下，混蛋!掉它! FBI! Drop the
gun right now, asshole! Drop it!
——去你妈的!-去你妈的，伙计!
- Fuck you! - Fuck you too, pal!
-我死了，她也死了。——嘿,莱昂!
- I die, she dies. - Hey, Leon!
把枪放下。放下!
Put the gun down. Put it down!
没人说要回去。
Nobody said anything about going back.
等大家都安全了，我们再谈这些，好吗?
We can talk about all that,
你撒谎!你撒谎!
when everybody's safe, okay?
You've lied! You all lied!
你不会想伤害她的，伙计。她是你的女儿。 You don't want to
hurt her, man. She's your daughter.
——好吗?她需要你。-你什么都不知道。 - Okay? She needs you.
- You don't know shit.
我知道你不想这样。
I know you don't want this.
我们都不想这样，好吗?
None of us wants this, okay?
拜托，你是个父亲。
Come on, you're a father.
把枪放下。
Put the gun down.
爸爸!爸爸!
Papa! Papa!
爸爸!
Papa!
-放开我!Beatriz,没有。
- Let go of me! Beatriz, no.
-快点，退后!——爸爸!爸爸!
- Come on, get back! - Papa! Papa!
-把她找回来!——放手!
- Get her back! - Let go!
爸爸!
Papa!
放开!
Let go!
Papa Leon?
是的,我,嗯…等等，塞拉，我想确认一下。
Yeah, I, uh--
Hold on, Serra, I wanna make
sure I'm clear on this.
你整个调查的关键，关键就躺在运肉车里脑袋被砸碎了吗? The lynchpin,
the key to your whole investigation
is laying in a meat wagon
with his brains smashed in?
-文森特救了很多人，长官-那混蛋死得很惨 Vincent saved lives,
sir. The fucker was going out messy.
我不在乎，阿米斯特德。
I don't care, Amistead.
我关心的是一项为期11个月的调查，它在边境两边都耗费了大量资源。
What I care
that has taken considerable resources
about, is an eleven
month investigation</font></font>
-现在彻底完蛋了。——不是。
on both sides of the border.
- Is now well and truly fucked.
- Not necessarily.
不要雪上加霜。
Don't add insult to injury.
没有合法身份的孩子不是贩卖人口的依据。
An undocumented child is not something
那到底是什么?
we build a trafficking case on.
先生。
Well, what the fuck is?
我们明早再谈。
Sir.
We'll talk in the morning.
毛里西奥。
Mauricio.
亚历克斯!
Alex!
这是什么?这是什么?
What's this? What's this?
天啊，她长大了!
Oh, my God, has she grown!
——嗯。-多可爱的孩子!
- Hmm. - What a sweet kid!
啊,夹马……很贵。
Ah, Pinches horses... expensive.
-我想还不如离婚。——是的!
- Less than a divorce, I guess. - Yeah!
瓜达拉哈拉干得不错。
Nice work in Guadalajara.
那城市就是个他妈的屎坑。
That city is a fucking shithole.
和这里一样。
Same as here.
我讨厌城市，人群，气味，还有该死的gueros。
I hate cities, the crowds,
the smells, the fucking gueros.
-没有栅栏。——没有。
- No offence. - None taken.
国家现在好多了，你不觉得吗?
Country's better now, don't you think?
还记得Tamalpais吗?
Remember Tamalpais?
那些是泽塔的人渣。
Those were Zeta scumbags.
疯狂的日子。不过,有趣的是吗?
Crazy days. Fun though, huh?
毛里西奥，这可不是我想要的乐趣。
Uh, not exactly my idea of fun, Mauricio.
对……你很敏感。一个艺术家。
Right...
You're sensitive. An artista.
耶稣。振作起来!
Jesus. Cheer up!
现在的生活很好。这是平静的。
Life is good now. It's calmer.
钱多了，血少了。
More money, less blood.
我们的朋友给你准备了好东西。
Our friends got you something nice.
毛里，你想要别人。
Mauri, you want someone else.
我现在还没准备好。
I'm not up for it right now.
起来吧。
Get up for it.
工作在埃尔帕索。你是那里人，对吧?
Job's in El Paso. You're from there, right?
又一个说不的理由。
Another reason to say no.
我想告诉你，我要出去。
I'm trying to tell you, I'm getting out.
来杯冰茶，谢谢。
Uh, an iced tea, por favor.
搞什么?
The fuck?
你喝醉了吗?
You drunk?
…不，只是累了。
U-- uh, no, no, just tired.
亚历克斯。我需要你帮忙。
Alex. I need you on this.
你了解这个城市。
You know the town.
它是太多了。
It's too much.
这是两个人的工作。
The job is for two.
你在埃尔帕索不是有个兄弟吗?
Don't you have a brother in El Paso?
毛里……你在监视我吗?
Mauri...
我们的工作就是了解情况，亚历克斯。
Are you spying on me?
It's our job to know things, Alex.
所以别再提退休的事了。
So stop talking this retirement shit.
我们这样的人是不会退休的。
Men like us don't retire.
给你，马歇尔先生，都准备好了。
Here you go Mr. Marshall, you're all set.
还有什么需要我帮忙的吗?
Anything else I can do for you?
马歇尔先生?
Mr. Marshall?
不，不，谢谢。我很好。
No, no, thank you. I'm fine.
请再说一遍房间号码?
The room number again?
11-0-6。在钥匙架上。
11-0-6. It's on the key holder.
啊,是的。谢谢你！
Ah, yes. Thank you.
请伏特加马提尼。
Vodka Martini, please.
现在喝酒太早了吗? So, too early in
the day for a glass of wine?
还是说喝血腥玛丽太晚了?
Or too late for a Bloody Mary?
我想这取决于你想过什么样的一天。
Guess that depends on what kind of day
这取决于你，不是吗?
you wanna have.
That's up to you, isn't it?
你独自吗?
Are you alone?
不是现在。
Not right now.
原谅我。
Excuse me.
——旅途愉快吗?-我们继续吧。
- Pleasant trip? - Let's get on with it.
是的，他在这里。
Uh, yes, he's here.
他看起来和你想的一样。
He looks like what you'd expect.
我相信他会没事的。
I'm sure he'll be fine.
好吧。现在再见。
Alright. Bye now.
你的人说很快就能搞定。
Your people said this will be done quickly.
它会。
And it will.
我需要更具体的说法。 I'm gonna need a little
more specificity than that.
不,你不会的。
No, you won't.
你知道的越少越好。
The less you know, the better.
我是想救他。
I was trying to save him.
你是个骗子。
You are a liar.
碧翠丝，你的遭遇。
Look, Beatriz, what happened to you.
爸爸做的事是不对的。
What Papa did, it ain't right.
这不是你的错。
Now, it's not your fault.
-任何儿童都不应该接受治疗…——爸爸说……“这是你获得自由的代价。” - No
child should be treated-- - Papa said...
"It is how you pay to be free."
那里比这里好多了。
It was better than here.
-我给你带了这个。-我不要!
- I brought you these. - I don't want them!
听着，有一种特殊的签证可以让你这样的人留在美国，而我们正在为你的…你想让我说出来。
Listen, there is, uh,
a special visa for... people like you
to stay in the US, while
we're working on your...
你被关在这里而伤害你的人却逍遥法外，这是不对的。
You want me to tell.
It's wrong that you're locked up here
while the men who did things
to you are out there.
爸爸说永远不要说。
Papa said to never tell.
我会把你转到儿童保护机构，好吗?
I'm gonna have you transferred
to Child Protective Services, okay?
他们会把你送去教养院。不是把你关起来。 They'll put you
in a group home. Not lock you up.
现在，我不期待任何回报。
Now, I don't expect anything in return.
好吧，你想说就说吧。
Okay, if you wanna talk, you can talk.
如果你不想，你可以不做。
If you don't wanna, you don't have to.
看来今晚我要单飞了。
Looks like I'm going solo tonight.
我得把这个做完。
I gotta get this done.
我在市中心申请许可证。
I've got a permit filing downtown.
——市中心吗?-是的，我工作，温迪。
- Downtown? - Yeah, I work, Wendy.
合同不会直接跳上船。
Contracts don't just jump in the boat.
别等我了。——艾利斯? Don't
wait up for me.
Ellis?</font></font>
——是吗?-她的香水真他妈的臭。
- Yeah? - Her perfume fucking stinks.
回家前把它洗掉，好吗?
Wash it off before you come home, will you?
哦,该死!
Oh, shit!
拜托!
Please!
——请!-你知道我为什么来这里!
- Please! - You know why I'm here!
……这都是误会。
It's-- it's all a misunderstanding.
这总是一个误会。
It's always a misunderstanding.
M……拜托!——在哪里?
- M-- Please! - Where?
……在保险箱里。楼上。拜托!
It's-- it's in the safe. Upstairs. Please!
不要这样做!
Don't do this!
我什么都没说，好吗?
I didn't, I didn't say anything, alright?
事情本不该发展到这一步的。 It wasn't, it
wasn't supposed to go this far.
如果我在这里，那就太过分了。
If I'm here, it's gone too far.
在这里,好吧!好吧!
It's here, alright! Okay!
——好的。——打开它!
- Okay. - Open it!
好吧,我只是……好吧。
Alright, I just... Okay.
听着，如果我给你…——来吧!——好的。
Look, if I give it to you--
- Come on! - Alright.
哦,爸爸?你回家吗?
Oh, Dad? You home?
我要去安娜贝尔家。
I'm going over to Annabelle's.
我可能会在这过夜，好吗?
I'll probably stay over, okay?
只是让你知道。
Just letting you know.
也许你想晚点再做。
Maybe you want to do that later.
嗯,我是多任务。
Uh-huh, I'm multi-tasking.
是啊，我只是不想今天就死。
Yeah, well I just don't wanna die today.
你住在德州怎么可能不说西班牙语? How can you live
in Texas and not speak Spanish?
该死的猫头鹰!
Fucking owl!
嗨,丹尼。他在哪里?
Hey, Danny. Where is he?
除了在我的犯罪现场乱踩?
Besides stomping all over my crime scene?
他在那里。
He's out there.
塞拉探员，阿米斯特德探员，这是范·坎普太太。 Agent Serra,
Agent Amistead, this is Mrs. Van Camp.
温迪，我保证这两个是我最好的。 Wendy, I guarantee
these are two of my best.
把你跟我说的告诉他们。
Just tell them what you told me.
埃利斯是……这是一起抢劫。
Ellis was...
It was a robbery.
保险箱被打开了。
The safe was opened.
你把这些告诉莫拉警探了吗?
And you've told this to Detective Mora?
我还没跟警察谈过。
I haven't talked to the police.
我先给杰拉尔德打了电话。
I called Gerald first.
我相信努斯鲍姆探员已经跟你说得很清楚了，我们越早着手调查越有可能破案。
Well, I'm-- I'm sure Special Agent Nussbaum
has made it clear to you,
the more people we have
working on this early on...
我去找莫拉警探，这样你就不用重复你的话了。
the better our chances of solving it.
Uh, so, I'm gonna go get Detective Mora,
just so you don't have to repeat yourself.
原谅我。
Excuse me.
你想出来给她录口供吗? You wanna come
outside and take her statement?
…你老板是想买还是已经买了?
So...
your boss trying to get some
or is he already getting it?
真不错，莫拉。
That's real nice, Mora.
把被害人的妻子性感化。
Sexualizing the wife of a murder victim.
没人找你们。
No one asked for you guys.
他只是空降进来的。
He just parachuted in on this.
我完全同意你的观点。
Yeah, couldn't agree with you more.
这是你的调查。
This is your investigation.
但让我们一起做这件事然后我会让努斯鲍姆不再烦你。
But let's just do this, together
and then I'll get Nussbaum off your back.
我不需要做什么交易。
I don't need to cut a deal.
你能不能别老是这么混蛋? Can you just not
be an asshole all the time?
说"好"吧，丹尼。
Just say "yes", Danny.
——是的,丹尼。-好吧，我们走。
- Yes, Danny. - Okay, let's go.
范坎普太太，这位是丹尼·莫拉警探。 Mrs. Van Camp,
this is Detective Danny Mora.
夫人，请节哀顺变。
Sorry for your loss, ma'am.
你最后一次见到活着的丈夫是什么时候? When's the last
time you saw your husband alive?
昨晚……9点左右。
Last night... around 9:00.
…我要去参加一个艺术开幕式。
I-- I was going to an art opening.
Ellis……他打算申请许可证。
And Ellis was...
He was going to file permits.
听起来你丈夫有外遇。 Sounds like your husband
had something on the side.
我以为他是去见朋友了。 I assumed that he
was, um, meeting a friend.
-你有她的电话，或者他的…——琳达。
- You have her number, or his-- Linda.
让塞拉探员继续审问。 Let's have Agent
Serra continue the interview.
我可以给你她的电话号码。
I can get you her number.
谢谢你,女士。
Thank you, ma'am.
你有没有生意上出了问题，你认识的人有没有想伤害他的?
You have any business dealings
that went bad, anyone you
know might wanna hurt him?
呃,…我不知道。
Uh, I-- I-- I don't know.
请帮助我!
Please help me!
我该怎么跟艾米说?
What am I gonna say to Em?
不要期望太多。
Don't expect too much.
当阿兹海默症突然发作时...我知道它是怎么开始的。 When the
onset of Alzheimer's is this sudden--
I know how it starts.
嘿,伙计。
Hey, pal.
是我，亚历克斯，你弟弟。
It's me, Alex, your brother.
你看起来很不错。
You're looking good.
你猜怎么着?
Guess what?
前几天我发现了这个。
I found this the other day.
1969. 让我想起了你。
1969. Made me think of you.
还记得那一年吗?啊? 选秀？
You remember that year? Huh? The draft?
太阳和雄鹿。
The Suns and the Bucks.
两人在首轮选秀中并列。
Both tied for the First Round Pick.
到抛硬币的时候，凤凰城猜正面。
Down to a coin flip... Phoenix calls heads.
对，是反面。
Yeah, it was tails.
雄鹿队得到了卢·阿尔辛多。
And the goddamn Bucks get Lew Alcindor.
是啊，我不怎么看篮球了。 Yeah, I don't
watch basketball much anymore.
我不记得上次是什么时候了。
Can't say I remember the last time I did.
我的队长今天早上来过电话。
My Captain called this morning.
显然，我不再被需要了。
Apparently, I'm no longer needed.
很好，很高兴大家都来了。
Good, I'm glad everybody's here.
鉴于Papa Leon袭击案的发生，特遣队正在重组。 So... in light
of what happened with the Papa Leon raid
the Task Force is being reorganized.
马尔克斯警探就要回墨西哥了。 Detective Marquez
will be heading back to Mexico.
我们还没说完，长官。
We're not done, sir.
与墨西哥警方的合作…我们受够了，塞拉，我这三天都在听华盛顿的唠叨，事实就是事实。
Cooperation with the Mexican Police has--
We're done, Serra, I've
spent the last three days
getting an earful from
Washington, facts are facts.
这是一项广泛的国际调查但我们一无所获。 This has been a wide
reaching international investigation
and we got nothing to show for it.
你有话要说吗，马奎斯?
You have something you wanna say, Marquez?
不是没事，先生。
It's not nothing, sir.
我们在墨西哥有很多。
We've gotten plenty in Mexico.
但我们一到美国，事情就…我不知道，也许你在华盛顿的耳朵就是不想听。
But as soon
I don't know, maybe your ears in Washington
as we come into the
US, things get, uh...</font></font>
just don't wanna hear.
很明显，对大鱼的胃口到此为止了。 It's pretty
obvious the appetite for big fish,
我不喜欢你的暗示，马奎斯。
ends at the border.
我不认为我在暗示什么。 I don't like what
you're insinuating, Marquez.
I don't think I was insinuating anything.
说得很直白。
Was saying it pretty flat out.
Hugo说得有道理，长官。
Hugo has a point, sir.
我们在美国的Padrote没有任何进展。 We've never gotten
anywhere with the US-based Padrote.
如果真有这种东西的话。
If there even is such a thing.
据说Papa Leon是为有钱人服务的。白人男性。 The word was
Papa Leon served rich men. White men.
"那个词"是你们在华雷斯办案的依据吗?
"The Word," is that what you people
我们有Papa Leon吹嘘他客户的录像。
build cases on in Juarez?
We have Papa Leon on tape
我知道你觉得这是针对你。
bragging about his clientele.
Look, I know you take this personally.
但是井干了。
But the well's gone dry.
我知道你不愿相信有个白人帕洛特，但结束一个案子并不代表就有了。
I know you
don't want to believe
there's a white Padrote,</font></font>
-小心点，塞拉。-我们有目击证人
but shutting down a case don't make it so.
- Watch yourself, Serra.
- We have a witness.
我们有个非法未成年人被拘留了。
What we have...
我们有一个严重精神创伤的未成年人被拘留了。
is an undocumented minor in detention.
What we have is a severely traumatized,
undocumented minor in detention.
她是我们唯一有价值的证人。 And she's the
only valuable witness we have.
你打算什么时候告诉我。
When were you gonna tell me you offered
比阿特丽丝·莱昂T-1签证?
Beatriz Leon a T-1 visa?
我正要说到这个。
I was coming to that.
通知我你无权做的交易吗?
To notify me of the deal
在你没有立案的案子里找证人?
you're not authorized to make?
我以为帮助比阿特丽丝·里昂这样的孩子是我们工作的一部分。
With a witness in a case you haven't made?
I thought helping kids like Beatriz Leon
——她的资格。—任务组完成。
was part of our job.
- She's eligible. The Task Force is done.
这是直接来自华盛顿的。
And that is straight from Washington.
至于碧翠丝，我们可以对她进行T-1处理把她转移到教养院，但你得专注于范·坎普的谋杀案。
As for
Beatriz, we can T-1 her and
move her to a group home,</font></font>
but you need to focus
on the Van Camp murder.
那是埃尔帕索警局，每天都是。
That's El Paso PD, every day.
你想帮助比阿特丽斯这样的孩子吗?
You want to help a kid like Beatriz?
你在谋杀案上合作。
You play ball on the homicide.
是的,好的。
Yeah, okay.
谢谢您,先生。
Thank you, sir.
好。
Good.
科尔曼,豪。
Coleman, Howe.
本周你会有新的任务分配。
You'll have new duty assignments this week.
马尔克斯警探，我代表联调局和美国政府，感谢你的服务。
Detective Marquez, on behalf of the Bureau
and the United States, I
thank you for your service.
我看过文件了，她是目击者还是受害者? I saw the
paperwork, is she a witness or victim?
两者都有。
Both.
我会联系社会服务部门，看看能不能在心理咨询和学校方面做些什么。
I'll reach out to Social Services,
see what we can do about
counseling and school.
那太好了。
That would be great.
边境两边有我该知道的家庭吗?
Is there any family on either side
of the border I should know about?
不，他父亲是个人贩子。
No, the father was a trafficker.
——嗯。-我要去道别了。
- Hm. - I'm gonna say goodbye.
我会随时通知你的。
I'll keep you posted.
我觉得你在这里会没事的。
I think you're gonna be okay here.
你之前在爸爸家问过我画什么。
You asked me before, at Papa's,
what I was drawing.
这是一片沙漠。
It is a desert.
我画的沙漠。
I draw deserts.
所以你做了，看看这个。
So you do, look at that.
保留它。
Keep it.
我一会儿再来看你，好吗?
I'll come back to see you soon, okay?
我向你保证。
I promise you.
操的缘故。
For fuck's sake.
她是一个孩子。
She's a child.
-这是个问题吗?-我不会这么做的。
- And that's a problem? - I won't do it.
你的人知道合同是给谁的。
Your people knew who the contract was for.
我他妈不会这么做的。你是聋人吗?
I fucking won't do it. Are you deaf?
也许我该给墨西哥城打个电话，听听他们怎么说。
Well, maybe I'll call Mexico City,
不,不。
see what they have to say about that.
No, no.
不，你要取消合同。
No, you're gonna call the contract off.
我他妈就是。
The fuck I am.
你是一个员工!我不接受他妈的…
You're an employee! I don't take fucking--
你想要这个吗?嗯?
You want this? Huh?
你取消合同。
You call the contract off.
你真的不知道你在玩什么。 You really don't
know what you're playing with.
哦，是的，我喜欢。
Oh, yes, I do.
波登先生。
Mr. Borden.
在银泉的Bienveneda大街22号。
Of 22 Bienveneda Avenue, Silver Springs.
女孩还活着。
The girl stays alive.
不然你就得对我负责
Or you're answerable to me.
混蛋。
Asshole.
不，请不要发表演讲或获奖。
No, no speeches or awards, please.
我的捐赠与我无关。
My donation isn't about me.
是的，你是对的。
Yes, you are correct.
这是我准备捐赠的金额，但是这次捐赠的建筑资金不能公开。
That is the amount I'm prepared to give,
however any construction funding
by this donation cannot be named
“达瓦纳·西尔曼翼。”
"The Davana Sealman Wing."
肯定是"海豹人之翼"
It must be simply, "The Sealman Wing."
我相信你能理解。
I'm sure you understand.
这样的给予是世代相传的。
Giving like this is generational.
他还在电话上吗?
Is he still on the line?
——是的,女士。-迈尔斯博士?
- Yes, ma'am. - Dr. Myers?
他三分钟前通过了安检。
He cleared security three minutes ago.
让他等着，直到我处理完这件事。
Have him wait, until I'm done with this.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我以为我说得很清楚了。
I thought I was clear.
办公室的电话从不打。
Never on the office number.
他知道。
William on speaker: He knows.
这有点模糊。
That's a bit vague.
他知道我的名字，我住在哪里，他不愿意做这份工作，他还有…他有范·坎普的u盘。
He knows my name, where I live,
and he won't do the job, and he's got...
He's got Van Camp's flash drives.
你说过他不会成为问题的。
You said he wasn't going to be a problem.
我要给墨西哥城打电话。
I'm going to call Mexico City.
这是一个解决方案。
That's one solution.
一个明显的和不微妙的。
An obvious and unsubtle one.
他想要什么?
What does he want?
取消那女孩的合同。 To have the contract
on the girl called off.
我们这么做，他就会交出情报。
We do that, he turns over the info.
这是有道理的。
There's something to be said for that.
你不能相信他。
William on speaker: You can't trust him.
我没说我信任他。
I didn't say I trusted him.
我说，我理解他的观点。
I said, I see his point of view.
我知道硬盘里有什么。
Look, I know what's on that drive.
兰迪的怪癖很明显。
Randy's pretty obvious about his quirks.
我不愿意跟你谈这个，威廉。
This is not a conversation
I'm comfortable having with you, William.
哦，上帝啊，他知道! William on speaker:
Oh, Jesus Christ, he knows!
关于那个女孩，关于我。
About the girl, about me.
我将处理它。
I'll handle it.
别再给我打电话了。
And don't call me again.
老实说，事情是这样的，如果你想听我的意见，这是真的吗?
Honestly, how it works,
if you want my opinion, is this the truth?
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
谢谢您，先生。
Thank you kind, sir.
好吧，就像我说的，事实…好吧,好吧,等等。我的错。
Okay, as I was saying, the truth...
Well, well, wait. My bad.
干杯,再次。
Cheers, again.
所以，也许我们应该上楼去，做个交易，因为今天结束的时候，我只想要个美女。
So, maybe we should just go upstairs,
make some sort of a deal,
'cause at the end of the day,
小点声。
all I want is a blowie.
Keep your voice down.
嘘，我们说好了。
Shh, we got a deal.
我会小点声，但我们还是得谈判。
I'll keep my voice down,
but we still got to negotiate.
嘿，离这位女士远点，伙计。
Hey, leave the lady alone, pal.
等一下，老爷子。
Whoa, whoa, wait a minute, pops.
首先，这不是女人。
First of all, this ain't no lady.
你马上就会知道了，对吧。宝贝吗?
Which you're about to find out
不,你喝醉了。去睡觉。
right about now, am I right. babe?
No, you're drunk. Go to bed.
好吧，你能帮我们个忙吗，求你了，滚出去…
Okay, can you do us a favor, please
and get the fuck out of here--
他妈的!
Fuck!
你他妈开什么玩笑?
Are you fucking kidding me?
去你妈的!
Fuck you!
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我很抱歉。这是令人尴尬的。
I'm sorry. It's embarrassing.
他只是个酒吧里的酒鬼，在美女面前表现得很混蛋。
He's just a drunk at a bar,
being an asshole in front
of a beautiful lady.
这种事经常发生。
Happens all the time.
谢谢。
Gracias.
龙舌兰酒!
Tequila!
拜托，至少我在努力，Hugo。
Oh, come on, at least I'm trying, Hugo.
你去。
U-go.
尤格。
Ugo.
他们就是不想知道，对吧?
They just don't wanna know, do they?
以小的胜利为例。
Take the little victories.
贝亚特里斯已经被释放了。
Beatriz is out of detention.
为什么六?
Why six?
你不会想知道的。
You don't want to know.
事实上,我做的。
Actually, I do.
我在华雷斯办一个案子。
I was working on a case in Juarez.
死去的女孩。
The Dead Girls.
想象一下，那么多女人消失了，你却无能为力。
Imagine, so many women disappear
and you can't do nothing.
他们说每个人都有自己的号码。
They say everyone has their number.
对警察来说，他们只是数字。
For the police they're all just numbers.
六个?
Six?
Emiliana Manteras当时13岁。
Emiliana Manteras was 13 years old.
她辞去了在马奎拉多拉的工作，然后消失了。 Left her job
at a Maquilladora and disappeared.
就消失了。
Just gone.
四个月后，几个孩子在垃圾堆里发现了她的尸体。
Four months later, a couple of kids
found her body in a dump.
她的母亲，她的姐妹。
Her mother, her sisters.
他们是强大的。
They were strong.
他们把艾米丽安娜的照片贴在了全市总部的墙上。 They plastered
Emiliana's photo on the walls
of headquarters in all the city.
问题不在于没有人知道女孩发生了什么。
The problem wasn't that no one knew
每个人都知道。
what happened to the girl.
Everyone knew.
艾米丽安娜和一个士兵上了一辆车。
Emiliana got into a car with a soldier.
阿图罗Pontilla。
Arturo Pontilla.
Pontilla喜欢和毒枭聚会。
Pontilla liked to party with the Narcos.
我跟着他。
I followed him.
我不动声色地立案了。
I built the case quietly.
但由于庞蒂利亚是军人，起诉必须先交给他的指挥官，然后他们就他妈的把他转移到锡那罗亚。
But since Pontilla was military,
the indictment had to go
to his commander first
and they just fucking
transfer him to Sinaloa.
三个星期后，艾米丽安娜的母亲、姨妈和三个姐妹失踪了。
Three weeks later, Emiliana's mother,
aunt and three sisters disappeared.
他们把那些女人吊在桥上就在我办公室窗户前。
They hung those women from a bridge
right in front of my office window.
耶稣。
Jesus.
你应该学习祷文。
You should learn the prayer.
嘿!
Hey!
嘘!嘿!
Shh! Hey!
你是好的。
You're okay.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是玛雅。
I'm Maya.
你在酒店。
You're at the hotel.
——酒店?——是的。
- Hotel? - Yes.
做了个噩梦。
Just had a bad dream.
你是好的。
You're okay.
很好，也许下次你来的时候…我不会回来了。 That was nice,
maybe next time you're in town--
I won't be back.
好吧。
Alright.
-祝你好运!-也敬你。
- Good luck then! - And to you.
一个13岁的女孩在日落高地被谋杀了。
Woman on TV: A 13-year-old girl
has been murdered in Sunset Heights.
这名未成年人名叫比阿特丽斯·莱昂(Beatriz
Leon)，最近刚从埃尔帕索拘留所转移到一个教养院。
had recently been relocated to a group home
The minor, Beatriz Leon,
from an El Paso detention center.
根据埃尔帕索警方发言人的说法，那个女孩的谋杀案是…我昨晚在这儿吗?
According to an El Paso police spokesman,
the young girl's murder is...
Was I here last night?
是的。怎么了?
Yes. What's wrong?
我们得到的细节非常少……-你确定?——是的! Woman on TV:
We're getting very few details...
- You sure? - Yes!
-我在这里?——是的!
- I was here? - Yes!
——一整夜?——是的!住手，你受伤了……-我整晚都在这里?——是的。 - All
night? - Yes! Stop it, you're hurting--
- I was here all night? - Yes.
仔细听我说。
Listen to me. Very carefully.
你必须马上离开。
You have to leave now.
你没来过，我们也没见过面。
You were never here, we never met.
-你明白吗?——我明白了。
- Do you understand? - I understand.
我得走了。对吧?
I have to go. Right?
你暂时别再来这家酒店了。
You stay away from this hotel for a while.
-很长时间!——好的。
- A long while! - Okay.
-你听到了吗?——是的!
- Do you hear me? - Yes!
不要替任何人开门。任何人!
Do not answer that door for anyone. Anyone!
值得注意的是，针对儿童的暴力行为执行得当，是边境另一边贩毒集团的名片。 Woman
on TV: Well executed, it is worth noting
that violence against children,
is a calling card of the cartels
当市长被要求发表评论时，他没有得到任何回应。
across the border.
Called on for comment, the Mayor had none.
嘿!你忘了吃药...回来!回来! Hey! You forgot
them, you forgot your pills--
Get back! Get back!
你什么时候变软了，亚历克斯?
When did you go soft, Alex?
他们会杀了你的。
They'll end you for this.
退休快乐,Maury !
Happy retirement, Maury!
亚历克斯!
Alex!
天啊，你有一颗35岁的心。 Goodness, you got
the heart of a 35-year-old.
照这样下去，你能活到130岁。
At this rate, you'll live to be 130.
我给你五百万，把它变成135。
I'll give you five million to make it 135.
如果你答应了，我就炒了你。
If you said, "Yes," I'd fire you.
你知道如果我答应了，我会希望你答应的。
You know if I said yes, I'd want you to.
我祖父是阿布鲁泽人。他活到了104岁。 My grandfather
is a Abruzzese. He lived to be 104.
是吗?幸运的人。
Yeah? Lucky guy.
你知道，沿着亚得里亚海的所有地区，还有日本冲绳，他们称之为蓝色区域。 You
know, that all region, along the Adriatic,
and Okinawa, Japan, they
call those blue zones.
那些百岁老人比例较高的地方。
Places that generally have
a higher percentage of centenarians.
我知道,约瑟夫。但是为什么呢?
I'm aware, Joseph. But why?
营养?空气中缺乏污染物?
Nutrition? Lack of pollutants in the air?
我们没有理由衰老，衰老。 There is no reason
we have to age, to decay.
一些医学专业人士可能会这么说。 Some medical
professionals might actually argue that.
一切都可以被重新编程，修改。
Everything can be reprogrammed, modded.
为什么人类的健康不应该是一样的呢?
Why shouldn't human health be the same?
DNA的一种算法。
DNA's an algorithm.
听着，我不会告诉你怎么花钱。 Look, I'm not gonna
tell you how to spend your money.
尤其是这么多钱最后都进了你的口袋。
Especially when so much of it
ends up in your pocket.
谢谢你给我打电话。
I appreciate you giving me a call.
我不知道这镇上到底发生了什么。 I don't know what
the fuck is going on in this town.
对天发誓，这里越来越像阿富汗了。 Swear to God, it's
getting more like Afghanistan every day.
-他们是谁?——匹配集。
- Who are they? - Matched set.
Jane和Joe Doe。
Jane and Joe Doe.
他坐在驾驶座上，被炸飞了。 He was in the
driver's seat, blown the fuck up.
她在后备箱里。
She was in the trunk.
点32口径子弹击中颈部，有压制痕迹。
.32 caliber bullet to the neck,
就像我们从比阿特丽斯·莱昂身上撤资一样。
jacketed with suppressor markings.
Just like we pulled out of Beatriz Leon.
车主是大卫·马歇尔。
Car's registered to a David Marshall.
在机场租的。
Rented at the airport.
一个从圣地亚哥来的商人。
Some expat businessman out of San Diego.
可能是车里的尸体。
Probably the corpse in the car.
我们正在对他们俩进行牙齿测试。
We're running teeth on them both.
这家伙喝得烂醉如泥。
Okay, this guy is drunk as a skunk.
他用一把点24口径的枪开了三次。 He, uh, pulled a
.24 three times over the limit.
所以我需要你在走之前在报告上签字。 So I need you to
sign off on the report before you go.
你明白了。
You got it.
——那是什么?-在地板上找到的。
- What's that? - Found them on the floor.
数据库里没有匹配，所以实验室正在做化学测试。
It didn't match anything on our database,
so the lab is running chem-test.
如果这是处方，可能会有帮助…实验室正在研究，我们也许不华丽，文森特，但我们不蠢。
If that's a prescription, it might help--
The lab's on it, we might not be fancy,
Vincent, but we ain't dumb.
我去搜索马歇尔的名字，看能不能查到。
I'll run the Marshall name through VICAP,
弹道报告一出来我就告诉你。药片也是一样。
see if anything comes up.
I'll hit you up with the ballistics
as soon as they come back.
Same with the pill.
Yeah, thanks.
嘿!
Hey!
那女孩的事我很抱歉，伙计。这太糟糕了。 Sorry about
the girl, man. It was fucked up.
我回不去了。
I couldn't go back.
墨西哥人不再爱你了吗?
They don't love you in Mexico anymore?
你不是在征求我留下的许可吧? You're not asking for
my permission to stay, are you?
-琳达说我必须这么做-这样的话…别这样，你知道她是什么样的人。 - Linda
said I had to. - Oh, well, in that case--
Come on, you know what she's like.
是的。
Yeah.
没人在乎那个女孩，文森特。 Nobody gives a
fuck about that girl, Vincent.
除了你，我和琳达。
Except you, me and Linda.
我能做到你和她做不到的事。你知道吗? I can do things
you and her can't. You know?
作为一个关心的公民。
As a concerned citizen.
从墨西哥吗?
From Mexico?
好吧，关切的墨西哥公民。
Okay, concerned Mexican citizen.
在美国的调查权力有问题。
With questionable investigative
authority in the United States.
是啊，努斯鲍姆肯定会同意的。
Yeah, Nussbaum is really gonna go for that.
他妈的努斯鲍姆。我不为他工作。
Fuck Nussbaum. I don't work for him.
听着，我向你保证，除非你给我一个，否则我没有理由说这些。
Look, I promise you I had no reason
to say anything unless you give me one.
你现在做的事太愚蠢了，埃利斯。 What you're doing right
now is incredibly stupid, Ellis.
我希望你能理解。
I hope you understand that.
-你让我别无选择。-我不会出局的。 You've left me no choice.
I won't be cut out.
听着，没必要搞得这么难看。
Look, this doesn't have to be ugly.
勒索已经很丑陋了。
Blackmail is already ugly.
——看,所有…-范·坎普先生!
-Look, all-- -Mr. Van Camp!
我们不是在谈判。
We are not negotiating.
你已经越过了一条没有退路的线。 You've crossed a
line from which there is no return.
看起来是点32口径的。
Looks like another .32 caliber.
我猜它身上也会有压制标记。 And I'm guessing
it's also gonna be jacketed
with suppressor markings.
我去和他妻子谈谈。
I'm gonna go talk to the wife.
看到你在那里。
See you there.
你认为他是对的吗?
Do you think he's right?
我敢打赌。
I'd put money on it.
毫无疑问，这是个问题。
This is a problem, no question.
也许是一个打者在清理垃圾。
Maybe a hitter cleaning up some shit.
我回头再找你们。
I'll catch you guys later.
好主意。
Good idea.
据我所知，塞拉，你当时在调查范·坎普的谋杀案。
Nussbaum: Last time I checked, Serra,
据我所知，先生，我为联邦调查局工作。
you were working the Van Camp murder.
Last time I checked,
sir, I work for the FBI.
我刚才看到的是雨果·马尔克斯吗?
Was that Hugo Marquez I just saw?
听……我觉得比阿特丽丝·里昂，在市中心汽车后备-
箱里发现的无名女尸和这个叫威廉·博登的人之间有联系。
between Beatriz Leon, the Jane Doe found
Listen... I think
there's a connection
in the trunk of the car downtown
and this guy, William Borden.
如果这真的是一件。32人，有三个人可能是被同一把枪杀死的。 If this
does turn out to be a jacket of .32,
that's three people likely
killed with the same weapon.
听着，我明白，那个女孩。她在你的皮肤下面。 Look, I get it,
the girl. She's under your skin.
也许你有点痴迷于…我只是在做我的工作。
Maybe you're a little obsessed--
雨果认为这是职业杀手，用来报复。
I'm just doing my job.
Hugo thinks it's a pro, settling scores.
我们认为可能是栅栏那边的击球手。 We think it could
be a hitter from across the fence.
但你不能肯定。
But you can't be sure.
我们不能，但如果弹道吻合，而且真的有墨西哥杀手在镇上乱窜，我们可能得赶在那之前。
We
really is a Mexican killer
tearing ass through town,
can't, but if the
ballistics match, and there</font></font>
我们需要马奎斯
we might want to get ahead of that.
And we're gonna need Marquez.
好吧，做你该做的。
Alright, do what you have to do.
但我要一天更新两次。
But I want updates twice a day.
是的。
Yeah.
实验室刚查出那些药的情况。
Lab just came back on those pills.
Diffadyl。
Diffadyl.
阿尔茨海默氏症的药物。你的枪手开始失控了。 Alzheimer's drug.
Your shooter is loosing his shit.
——好的。妻子在里面吗?-是的。
- Okay. Is the wife inside? - Yeah.
把你的手从笼子里拿开。 Keep your hands
away from the cage on that one.
我不知道这是药物还是纯粹的疯狂。 I don't know if
it's medicine or just plain crazy.
-想旁听吗?——当然。
- Wanna sit in on this? - Sure.
波登夫人，我是塞拉探员。我是马奎斯警探。 Mrs. Borden, I'm
Agent Serra. This is Detective Marquez.
对发生的事我很抱歉。
I'm sorry for what's happened.
生活的一部分，对吧?
Part of life, right?
这是他们说的……还不太明白。
It's what they say...
Hasn't really sunk in.
嗯,美国联邦调查局。的意。
Hmm, FBI. Fancy.
-你也是探员?-墨西哥联络员。
- You an agent, too? - Liaison from Mexico.
墨西哥和威廉有什么关系?
What's Mexico have to do with William?
他讨厌这个地方。
He hated the place.
这就是我们想知道的。 Well, that's what we're...
hoping to find out.
你有没有注意到过去几周发生了什么不寻常的事，你丈夫的行为有什么变化吗?
Have you noticed anything unusual
happen in the past few weeks,
where your husband's
behavior has changed at all?
威尔的行为二十年来都没变。
Will's behavior hasn't changed in 20 years.
不。什么都没有。
No. Nothing.
-他做的是什么法律?——房地产。 - What kind of
law did he do? - Real Estate.
很抱歉这么问，波登夫人。
Sorry to ask this, Mrs. Borden.
但你知道你丈夫和卖淫有什么关系吗?
But do you know if your husband had
我不知道。坐下来。
any ties to prostitution?
I have no idea. Sit down.
帐单付账?
Bill paying for it?
看起来不像他。
Doesn't seem like him.
你丈夫认识Ellis Van Camp吗?
Did your husband know Ellis Van Camp?
我知道温迪。我在同样的场合见过她。
I know Wendy. I see her at the same events.
这里就是个大型鸡尾酒会。
It's all one big cocktail party up here.
你喜欢鸡尾酒吗，警探?
You like cocktails, Detective?
Margaritas? Pina Coladas?
谢谢你的帮助，波登夫人。
Thanks for your help, Mrs. Borden.
如果你需要什么，给我们打电话。
If you need anything, just give us a call.
恐怕不能打扰她。别他妈开口。
I'm afraid she can't be disturbed--
Don't even fucking start.
我一早上都在给你打电话。
I've been calling you all morning.
波登死了。有人执行他。
Borden's dead. Someone executed him.
如果他找到了波登，那他就快了。
And if he got to Borden, then he's close.
耶稣,妈妈……
Jesus, mum--
深呼吸。
Just take a breath.
布拉沃。
Bravo.
你得离开埃尔帕索。立即。
You need to leave El Paso. Immediately.
坐公司的飞机。
Take the company plane.
明天晚上怎么样，都安排好了……听我说。 What about tomorrow
night, it's all been arranged--
Listen to me.
明天派对结束后，你就飞去日内瓦。 Tomorrow, after
the party, you'll fly to Geneva.
待在家里，为你去戒毒所做准备。
Stay at the house and make arrangements
康复吗?
for you to check into rehab there.
如果事情和你有关，我们有麻烦了，你就去解决你的问题，这样我们就有时间悄悄请个好律师。
Rehab?
If things connect to you,
and we have a problem, you will be working
on your issues, which will buy us time
to quietly hire very good lawyers.
而且你需要帮助，兰迪。
Besides... you need help, Randy.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
我知道，宝贝。
I know you are, baby.
我知道你是。
I know you are.
完整的弹道报告出来了。
Full ballistics came back.
杀死比阿特丽斯和车里无名女尸的是同一把枪，但不是波登。两支32口径手枪，两支枪。
Same
but not Borden. Two .32s, two shooters.
gun killed Beatriz and
the Jane Doe in the car,</font></font>
交易,文森特·塞拉。
Trafficking, Vincent Serra.
是你把那女孩带去教养院的。 You're the one who
took the girl to the group home.
——不是吗?-你是谁?
- Weren't you? - Who is this?
马歇尔。大卫·马歇尔。
Marshall. David Marshall.
开发和跟踪。
Tap and trace.
大卫·马歇尔在市中心烧了一辆车。 Ah, David
Marshall burned up a car downtown.
这是你干的吗?
Is that your doing?
我不能再替你做你的工作了。
I can't keep doing your job for you.
那是什么工作?
What job is that?
-波登，范坎普。-他们对孩子们做的事。 Borden, Van Camp.
What they did to children.
你什么都没做。
You're not doing anything about it.
你是说你杀了William Borden?
Are you saying you killed William Borden?
和Ellis Van Camp?是的。
- And Ellis Van Camp? Yes.
那女孩呢?Beatriz莱昂。
And what about the girl? Beatriz Leon.
不是女孩。这是毛。
Not the girl. That was Mauricio.
车里的男人。
The man in the car.
你太慢了，没法让他们付出代价。他们太富有。 You're too slow
to make them pay. They're too rich.
-谁太有钱了?-律师，客户
- Who's too rich? The lawyer, the client.
客户是谁?
Who's the client?
你认识她吗?——谁? Did you know her?
Who?</font></font>
……那个女孩。…Beatriz。
The-- the-- the girl. B-- Beatriz.
一点。你在乎吗?
- A little. Did you care?
15秒。
Fifteen seconds.
我当然不相信。
I certainly did.
我想相信你是个好人，文森特。 I want to believe
that you are a good man, Vincent.
我是坏人。已经很长时间了。
I'm the bad man. Have been for a long time.
但他们必须受到惩罚。
But they have to be punished.
如果我不能完成这个…你必须完成。
If I can't finish this...
you have to.
他在楼下的公园里。
He's downstairs in the park.
嘿,移动!
Hey, move!
这是什么?
What is this?
他在耍我们。
He's fucking with us.
他只是说我们太慢了。
He's just telling us we're way too slow.
一个混蛋在剥削一个孩子我们要多久才能把他送上法庭?
We've got an asshole exploiting a kid
and how long is it taking
us to bring him to trial?
两到三年，对吧?
Two to three years, right?
他说他们太有钱了。
He said they're too rich.
现在，我们在贩卖人口上的每一步都被击退了。 Now, we've been
getting push back on the trafficking
every step of the way.
不，我觉得他，他在干掉那些我们干掉不了的毒贩。
No, I think he's, he's taking out
the traffickers that we couldn't.
离开我们的面包屑。
Leaving us breadcrumbs.
证明一个观点。
Proving a point.
嗯…侦探马尔克斯。
Well... Detective Marquez.
你监视我多久了?
How long were you watching me?
我刚到，波登夫人。
I just got here, Mrs. Borden.
你不应该让大门开着。
You shouldn't leave the gate open.
该发生的就会发生。
Whatever will be will be.
如果你看着我...没什么好担心的，对吧?
And if you're watching over me...
nothing to worry about, right?
你是个游泳健将。
You're a strong swimmer.
我身材不好。
I'm out of shape.
我是92年奥运会的候补队员。 I was an alternate
for the '92 Olympic team.
我17岁。这是我一生中最美好的时光。
I was 17. Best time of my life.
到了96年，我失去了一秒钟。
By '96, I'd lost a second.
这是它。
That was it.
完成了。
Done.
所以我没有在洛杉矶买Wheaties Box和英俊的丈夫，而是来到了这里。
So instead of a Wheaties Box
and a dashing husband in LA,
I ended up here.
在德克萨斯州。
In Texas.
你能把那个杯子递给我吗?
Could you pass me that glass?
当然。
Sure.
你想要什么，警探?
So, what do you want, Detective?
嗯…我不是来给你打扫泳池的。
Well...
I'm not here to clean your pool.
你不是真正的警察，对吧?
You are not a real cop here, are you?
我就是为此而来的。
That's why I'm here.
什么?不逮捕我?
What? To not arrest me?
你听你丈夫说起过一个叫大卫·马歇尔的人吗?
Have you ever heard your husband talk about
你不是来问我问题的
a man named David Marshall?
You didn't come here to ask me questions.
我也不是为了这个来的。
I didn't come here for that either.
我没插手威廉的事。
I stayed out of William's business.
妻子知道。
Wives know.
我不知道这个名字，但我听到他在讲电话。
I never knew the name,
他很紧张。他不想让我听到。
but I heard him on the phone.
He was nervous. He didn't want me to hear.
他说的是一个来自墨西哥城的人。 He was talking
about a man from Mexico City.
你之前怎么不说?
Why didn't you say something before?
因为跟他说话的人。
Because of who he was talking to.
Davana Sealman。
Davana Sealman.
所以我才什么都没说。
That's why I didn't say anything.
他被利用了。
He was being used.
如何?
How?
你应该去。
You should go.
谢谢你，波登女士。
Thank you, SenoraBorden.
别再回来了，马奎斯警探。
Don't ever come back, Detective Marquez.
Davana Sealman?你确定?
Davana Sealman? You sure?
这就是她说的名字。
That's the name she said.
博登可能是她的律师之一。
Borden was probably one of her attorneys.
没有，波登的名字不在海洋公司或达瓦纳·西尔曼个人提交的文件上。
Nope, Borden's name isn't listed
on any of the filings for Sea Corp
or Davana Sealman personally.
你知道我们在谈论的是国内最有权势的房地产大亨之一吧?
You realize we're
talking about one of
the most powerful</font></font>
real estate moguls in the country, right?
是的。是的。
Yeah. Yeah.
我知道，但波登在电话里跟西尔曼说了那个"墨西哥城来的人" I know, but
Borden spoke to Sealman on the phone
你有证据吗?那你至少上过她了吧?
about the "Man from Mexico City."
Oh, you got proof? Well,
did you bang her at least?
我是说，如果你要相信一个半醉半醉的花瓶老婆的话，你也会从中得到一些好处，对吧?
I mean,
trophy wife, you may as well get
something out of it, right?
if you're gonna take the
word of a half-drunk</font></font>
-她详细说明了吗?——什么?
- Did she elaborate? - What?
关于"来自墨西哥城的人"
On the "Man from Mexico City."
闭嘴，等等!
Shut up, hold on!
波登不是达瓦纳·西尔曼的律师。 Borden wasn't one
of Davana Sealman's lawyers.
他是兰迪·西尔曼的律师之一。
He was one of Randy Sealman's lawyers.
Davana的儿子。
Davana's son.
显然，兰迪也是个房地产大亨。 Apparently, Randy's
also a real estate mogul.
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
兰迪·西尔曼的公司拥有中央处理设施。 Randy Sealman's company
owns the Central Processing facility.
他们把碧翠丝送去了那里。
Where they sent Beatriz.
你可能没注意到，他们派了很多人去那里。
Hey, in case you haven't noticed,
哦，是的，我知道。
they send a lot of people there.
Oh, yeah, I know.
但她的13个。
But she's 13.
想象一下，在移民和海关执法中心，你在那个年龄感到多么脆弱。
Imagine how vulnerable you feel at that age
in an ICE center.
好吧，让我们看看。
Okay, let's take a look.
好吧。这不是她第一次去那里了。
Okay. Well, it's not her first time there.
去年她和她父亲在那里待了三周，然后他们被驱逐出境。
She was there last year for three weeks
它变得棘手。埃利斯·范·坎普是CPF的建设者。 with her
father, and then they were deported.
It gets stickier. Ellis Van
Camp was CPF's builder.
所有和这个处理中心有关的人，律师，建筑商，碧翠丝，都死了。 So everyone
associated with this Processing Centre,
the lawyer, the builder,
Beatriz, all dead.
他会杀了兰迪·西尔曼。
He's going to kill Randy Sealman.
♪ Deep in the night
♪ Where the music's gonna play
♪ When the music's here to
stay deep in the night ♪
♪ Come on
喝值班吗?
Drinking on duty?
这离官方说法还远着呢。
This is so far away from official.
这个人，他是看守所的老板。
So this guy,
he owns the detention center.
你想知道我们为什么要保护他吗? And you're wondering
why we're protecting him?
我一点也不奇怪为什么。
I don't wonder why at all.
♪ Deep in the night
Amistead吗?
兰迪在下层甲板，往里面走。
Amistead?
Randy is on the lower deck, moving inside.
-我在路上了。- Hugo，盯着甲板。
On my way. - Hugo, keep eyes on deck.
明白了。
Got it.
目标在船上!
Target's on the boat!
把那玩意儿脱了。
Take that shit off.
我离开时，锁上门。
When I leave, lock the door.
好吧?好姑娘。
Okay? Good girl.
你人渣。
You scum.
把它下来。
Put it down.
好啊!。
Attaboy.
你是文森特，对吗?
You're Vincent, aren't you?
我是。
I am.
我是亚历克斯。亚历克斯·刘易斯。
I'm Alex. Alex Lewis.
你知道那些人对那孩子做了什么，对吧? You know what those
people did to that child, right?
非常好。
Only too well.
我做过疯狂的事。
I've done crazy things.
但你永远不会伤害孩子。
But you don't hurt children, ever.
听着，为什么我们不…-只是谈谈?-没时间了。
Listen, why don't you and I just...
- Just have a talk? - No time for that.
我明白你为什么这么说。
I understand why you're saying that.
我知道你身体不好。
I know you're not well.
我们都得死，文森特。
We all have to die, Vincent.
重要的是你走之前做了什么……——文森特!把枪放下!-滚出去，滚出去! What's
important is what you do before you go--
- Vincent! Put your gun down!
- Get outta here get outta here!
-你朋友枪法好吗?——非常。
- Is your friend a good shot? - Very.
-那就看你的了。——不要动!
- Then it's in your hands. Don't move!
把他妈的枪放下!
Put the fucking gun down!
如果我死了，她就不会知道真相了。
If I'm dead, she'll never know the truth.
把枪放下。
Put the gun down.
嘿，嘿，嘿!-你他妈在干什么? Hey, hey, hey!
What the fuck are you doing?</font></font>
我懂了!
I've got it!
我15年前就戒酒了。
You know, I quit drinking 15 years ago.
但现在，我能从喉咙深处尝到威士忌的味道。 But right now,
I can actually taste the scotch
in the back of my throat.
戴瓦娜·西尔曼的独子在我眼皮底下被杀了。
Davana Sealman's only son
was just murdered on my watch.
她对我们不满意。
She's not happy with us.
这位女士甚至雇佣了下班的警察来保护她。 The lady has even
hired off-duty cops for protection.
他早在我们前面了。
He was way ahead of us.
他可能在派对开始前就在船上了。 He was probably on
that boat before the party even began.
这家伙是谁，文斯?
Who is this fucking guy, Vince?
Alex Lewis.
我可以告诉你他是美国人。
Well, I can tell you he's American.
毫无疑问他是个承包商，但我不认为这些都被击中了。
He's no doubt a contractor, but...
I don't think these have all been hits.
他想为比阿特丽丝·里昂报仇。
He wants revenge for Beatriz Leon.
先生,你还好吗?
Sir, you alright?
你今晚喝酒了吗，先生?
Have you been drinking tonight, sir?
……保罗和他的儿子们。
Paul...
Paul with his sons.
耶稣。
Jesus.
摩托车巡警埃里克·莱尔。
Motorcycle patrolman Eric Lyle.
一定是发现亚历克斯受伤了。
Must have found Alex wounded.
那辆野马上全是血。
There was blood all over the Bronco.
我不知道。也许他被吓到了。
I don't know. Maybe he got spooked.
那不是他的风格。
That's not his style.
他的风格就是谋杀，文森特。
His style is murder, Vincent.
不，我们得在埃尔帕索警局之前找到他。 No, we need to
find him before the El Paso PD.
他们不会高兴的。
They're not going to be happy about this.
我们知道一些他们不知道的事。
Well, we know something they don't.
我想我知道亚历克斯·刘易斯是谁了。
I think I know who Alex Lewis is.
我查了青少年犯罪记录。
I ran juvenile records.
汽车偷窃,破坏攻击。
Vandalism, auto-theft, assault.
有可能是他。
Well, it could be him.
唯一的问题是，亚历克斯·刘易斯死了。
Only problem is, Alex Lewis is dead.
四十年前，他和父亲在自家面包店的一场大火中丧生。 He and his father
died in the fire at the family bakery
调查人员认为是亚历克斯放的火。
forty years ago.
Investigators thought Alex set the fire.
不过哥哥还在城里。
Brother's still in town though.
公园路上的护理中心。
Care facility on the parkway.
先进的阿尔茨海默氏症。
Advanced Alzheimer's.
男人的一种蔬菜。
Man's a vegetable.
我还找到了医疗记录。
I also came up with medical records.
亚历克斯和他哥哥在急诊室很有名。 Alex and his
brother were well known at the ER.
总是"从楼梯上摔下来"或"意外烧伤" Always a "fall down
the stairs" or an "accidental burn."
其他事情则更难隐藏。
Other things were harder to hide.
父亲从未被指控虐待。
Father was never charged with the abuse.
性或物理。
Sexual or physical.
要我搜查面包店吗?
Want me to warrant the bakery?
肯定。
Definitely.
这个来自墨西哥城的家伙，就是博登跟戴瓦娜·西尔曼说过的那个。
This guy from Mexico City,
the one Borden was talking
to Davana Sealman about.
如果是她雇的呢?
What if she hired him?
因为我在想如果艾丽克丝不想亲自杀西尔曼，他想让我们把她带回来。
'Cause I'm thinking if Alex is not up
to killing Sealman himself,
Catch是唯一能联系上的人。
he wants us to bring her in.
Catch is, the only person who can connect
希尔曼对这一切…是亚历克斯。
Sealman to any of this--
她比其他任何一个都更难接近。
Is Alex.
She's harder to get to
than any of the others.
他来找你是为了赔钱。
He reached out to you to cover his bets.
保罗和亚历克斯的病历上只有面包店的地址。
The only address from Paul and Alex's
算了吧，那地方一团糟。
medical records is the bakery.
Oh, forget about it, that place is a wreck.
除非你在找一只鸽子。
Unless you're looking for a pigeon.
你说什么?
What did you say?
鸽子。
Pigeons.
Palomas。这地方到处都是。
Palomas. The place is full of them.
那辆野马的实验室报告...就是巡警被杀的那辆，地板上有鸽子粪的痕迹。
The lab report on the Bronco...
the one where the patrolman got killed,
the floor had traces of pigeon shit on it.
我能为你做点什么吗?
Anything I can get you?
什么?
What?
你需要什么?
Anything you need?
不了,谢谢。
No, thank you.
时间到了，孩子们。检查。
Top of the hour, boys. Check in.
老板!
Boss!
让他起来。
Let him up.
给他一个新电池。
Get him a new battery.
-把它们放下!——现在!
- Put them down! - Now!
你!回来!
You! Get back!
呆在这里。不要给任何人打开那扇门。 Stay in here.
Don't open that door to anybody.
孩子们!主办公室。直播射击! Boys! Main office.
Live shooter! Live shooter!
他往屋顶去了。
He's headed for the roof.
莫拉。
Mora.
莫拉，他在屋顶上。
Mora, he's on the roof.
收到。如果有机会，就把他干掉。
Copy. If you get the chance, put him down.
收到
Copy that.
一切都结束了。
It's all over.
我带你离开这里。
Let's get you out of here.
你杀了我儿子。
You killed my son.
是的。
Yes.
我知道你做了什么。
And I know what you've done.
撞针。
Firing pin.
你知道我刚才为什么不干掉你吗? You know why I
didn't just off you back there?
让我告诉你为什么。
Let me tell you why.
那是仁慈。
That would have been mercy.
不。我想看你去尤马。
No. I want to see you go to Yuma.
我保证他们会把你操死，老头。 Where I will make sure
they fuck you to death, old man.
你这个杀警察的混蛋。
You cop-killing piece of shit.
那个小女孩怎么样?
How about that little girl?
你知道他们会怎么对待伤害孩子的人吗? You know what
they do to people who hurt kids?
我会和FBI探员Vincent Serra谈谈。 I'll talk
to FBI Agent V-- V-- Vincent Serra.
没有其他人。
No one else.
他妈的联邦调查局。
Fuck the feds.
我们指控你三起谋杀。
We got you on three counts of murder.
你那把破枪跟博登和埃里克·莱尔警官匹配。
Your busted fucking gun matches Borden
他有妻子和两个孩子…丹尼!他需要看医生。
and Officer Eric Lyle.
Guy had a wife and two kids--
Danny! He needs a doctor.
不,他没有。
No, he doesn't.
我有一整天的时间，最后，我向上帝发誓，我会得到一份书面认罪书。 I've got
all day, and by the end, I swear to God,
I'll have me a written confession.
如果他拿着一把坏了的枪去追西尔曼，我们会听到些什么。
If he went after Sealman with a broken gun,
we'd have heard something.
我只是觉得他在最后。他什么都不记得了。 I just think he's at
the end. He ain't remembering things.
而且，产后抑郁症已经完全消失了。
And also, PPD has gone totally silent.
这是面包店的地址。
And this came from the bakery address.
它是什么?
What is it?
耶稣。你从哪儿弄来的?
Jesus. Where did you get this?
没关系。
It doesn't matter.
埃尔帕索警局拘留了亚历克斯·刘易斯我需要你把他移交给我们。
El Paso PD are holding Alex Lewis
and I need you to transfer
him into our custody.
让他成为他们的问题。
Let him be their problem.
你到底想站在哪一边? Which side of this
do you really want to be on?
我得跟他谈谈。
I need to talk to him.
但似乎权力很大的人不希望这种情况发生。
But it seems very powerful people
don't want that to happen.
你他妈的对他做了什么?
What the fuck did you do to him?
-他拒捕。-所以你要拆散他?
- He resisted arrest.
- So you had to bust him up?
他可是个警察杀手。
He's a cop killer for fuck's sake.
你喜欢被达瓦纳·西尔曼收买吗?
You like being on Davana Sealman's payroll?
嘿!
Hey!
冷静下来!
Cool off!
嗯,很好。
Well, well.
美国联邦调查局。
The FBI.
嗯。
Huh.
是你朝我开枪的。
You are the one that shot me.
我不会道歉的。
I'm not going to offer an apology.
我不是要你这么做。
I'm not asking for one.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
这些药撑不了多久了。
These aren't going to help for much longer.
我知道你想澄清这件事。
I understand you want to clear this up.
清楚呢?
Clear this up?
不。
No.
我要西尔曼死。
I want Sealman dead.
她没有正式的犯罪记录。 Well, she's not
officially tied to any crime.
你知道那不是真的。
You know that's not true.
她批准了这次袭击。
She sanctioned the hit.
她雇我去杀…两个人。
She hired me to kill... two people.
埃利斯·范·坎普，第二个就是那个孩子。 Ellis Van Camp
and the second was that child.
十三岁的女孩。…Beatriz。
Girl of thirteen. Be-- Be-- Beatriz.
我不会那样做的。
I won't do that.
不。
No.
不。你不能碰孩子。
No. You don't touch children.
-好的，按下。——谢谢。
Dr. Myers: Okay, press down. Thank you.
我真的很感激你在我身边。
I really appreciate you being here for me.
在这一切。
During all this.
你不只是一个客户。
You're not just a client, you know.
真的吗，约瑟夫?
Is that true, Joseph?
最难的事就是永远不要相信亲近的人。 You know, the hardest
thing is never really trusting
those people close to you.
除了兰迪……我永远不会知道为什么有人会和我在一起。
Besides Randy...
I will never really know
why someone is with me.
来吧。我是你的朋友，达瓦娜。
Come on. I'm your friend, Davana.
我一直在你身边。
I'm here for you.
你的律师费是一千万美元。 The retainer for
your services is $10 million.
我不能。
I can't.
你知道你在要求我做什么吗?
Do you realize what you're asking me to do?
我很抱歉。不。
I'm sorry. No.
-我发过誓。——起誓吗?
- I took an oath. - An oath?
就像结婚誓言?
Like a marriage vow?
你去了兰迪的派对。
You were at Randy's parties.
你以为我不知道吗?
You think I didn't know?
所以，让我们简单点。
So, let's make this simple.
1000万美元或因与未成年人发生性关系而被起诉和监禁。
$10 million or prosecution
and prison for sex with minors.
Davana……你需要了解一些事情。
Davana--
兰迪是弱。
You need to understand something.
但他是我儿子。
Randy was weak.
But he was my son.
你不是。
You are not.
-受雇杀人。-为了复仇而杀人。虐待儿童。 Murder for hire.
Murder for revenge. Child abuse.
都在这里了。
It's all here.
这不是结束。
It's not over.
每个人都死了,亚历克斯。
Everybody's dead, Alex.
即使你上了庭，你也会被判终身监禁，朋友，医生告诉我可能只有三到六个月。
Even if you
which from what the doctors tell me
do make it to trial, you
get life, my friend,</font></font>
is maybe three to six months.
那么，我们在这里做什么?
So, what are we doing here?
-我们为什么在这里?——Davana Sealman。
- Why are we here? Davana Sealman.
正义。
Justice.
正义?
Justice?
-你在开玩笑吗?-我可以作证…你是个职业杀手。 - Are you kidding
me? - I'll testify to all that--
You're a contract killer.
你觉得你的证词能在法庭上站得住脚吗? You think your
testimony's going to stand up in court?
-她雇我去杀一个孩子-你写下来了吗?
- She hired me to kill a child.
- Did you get that in writing?
我们需要那个证据。
We're gonna need that evidence.
你真以为我们能伸张正义吗?
You really expect we're gonna find justice?
我希望你试一试。
I expect you to try.
听着……我来告诉你什么是正义。
Listen...
Let me tell you something...
about justice.
十二个月前，一个醉酒司机开着偷来的车在8号州际公路上飞驰。
Twelve months ago,
a drunk driver was flying down the I-8
他嗑药嗑嗨了。
in a stolen car.
他没看到另一辆车停在路边。
He's high on meth.
He hasn't seen another car
一位母亲和她十岁的儿子。
that's pulled over on the shoulder.
A mom and her ten-year-old son.
从乐高乐园回家。他们的轮胎漏气了。 Coming home from
Legoland. They got a flat tire.
但是科尔维，他没看到那个女人在外面换轮胎。
But Colvey, he doesn't see that the woman
is out there changing the tire.
他直接撞到她身上。杀死了她。
He just plows right into her. Kills her.
现在，他停下车，看到身后那个男孩跳了出来。
Now, he stops his car
and he sees behind him
the boy's jumped out.
他显然尖叫。
He's obviously screaming.
看到他妈妈，死在路上，哭喊着求救。 Seeing his mom,
dead on the road, crying for help.
但柯维帮不上忙。
But Colvey doesn't help.
他倒车，从男孩身上倒了过去。 He puts his car in
reverse and backs over the boy.
确保没有目击证人
Making sure there's no witnesses.
然后他在两英里外的路上烧了车。 Then he torches
his car two miles down the road.
但是一个15岁的女孩，看到了他。
But a 15-year-old girl, she sees him.
她看到一个男人拿着煤气罐从大火中走出来。 She sees a man walking
away from a big fire with a gas can.
虽然不多，但足够让科尔维受审了。
Now, it ain't much, but it's enough
to put Colvey on trial.
你知道发生了什么吗?
You know what happened?
他们会照张相。
They do a photo line-up.
但那女孩，她没选柯维。
But the girl, she doesn't pick Colvey.
所以他们亲自来了，她也没有选柯维，尽管大家都知道是他。
So they do an in-person,
and again she doesn't pick Colvey,
even though everybody knows it's him.
三次，排成三排。
Three times, three line-ups.
每次她都选一个不同的男人。
Each time she picks a different guy.
然后Colvey就走了。
And Colvey walks.
他还逍遥法外。
And he's still out there.
所以记忆就是个混蛋。
So...
memory's a motherfucker.
至于正义…
And as for justice...
不能保证。
it ain't guaranteed.
你的妻子。
Your wife.
你的儿子。
Your son.
我有证据。
I have evidence.
是吗?你有什么证据?
Yeah? What evidence do you got?
-一个电话。——Davana Sealman。
A phone call. Davana Sealman.
……威胁我杀的第一个人。
Threatening...
Threatening the first man I killed.
Ellis Van Camp?
是的。我有一个翻转的电话……——Flash?——Flash。
Yes. I have that call on a... flip...
——闪存驱动器?——闪存驱动器。
- Flash? - Flash.
- Flash drive? - Flash drive.
在哪里?
Where is it?
我不知道。
I don't know.
帮我……帮我记住。
Help, help me...
Help me remember.
请。
Please.
我们会的。
We will.
这让我感到恶心。
That makes me sick to my stomach.
我很高兴那个混蛋死了。
I'm glad that bastard is dead.
他母亲在掩护他。
His mother was covering for him.
Davana Sealman?是的。
- Davana Sealman? Yeah.
那女人一辈子都没开过停车罚单。 That woman hasn't
had a parking ticket in her life.
她知道她的儿子在强奸未成年人。
She knew that her son was raping minors.
她还为埃利斯·范·坎普的死付了钱。 She also paid
for the hit on Ellis Van Camp.
根据什么证据?
Based on what evidence?
她雇的那个人，亚历克斯·刘易斯。他跟我说得很清楚。职业杀手的证词吗?
The man she
hired, Alex Lewis. He made
it very clear to me--</font></font>
Oh, the testimony of a professional killer?
亚历克斯·刘易斯被威廉·博登雇佣为达瓦纳·西尔曼工作。
Alex Lewis was hired by William Borden
这不是同一个人患有某种痴呆症吗?
for Davana Sealman.
Isn't this the same man
先进的阿尔茨海默氏症。
who has some kind of dementia?
是的,是的。
Advanced Alzheimer's.
听着，我需要真正的证据。
Yeah, yeah.
好吧，不仅仅是一个有认知障碍的杀人犯的证词。耶稣。
Look, I need real evidence.
Alright, not just the fucking testimony
of some murderer who's
cognitively impaired. Jesus.
任何像样的律师在证人席上都能打败他。 Any decent lawyer
would annihilate him on the stand.
听着，很显然，有一段戴瓦娜·西尔曼的电话录音明确地威胁了范·坎普。
Listen, apparently, there's a recording
of Davana Sealman on a phone call
explicitly threatening Van Camp.
-我可以利用这点。-我正在努力。 - Well, that I can use.
- I'm working on it.
你把音频给我，如果证据确凿，我就立案。 Well, you bring
me the audio, and if it's solid,
I'll make the case.
谢谢您,先生。
Thank you, sir.
你确定你准备好了吗?
Are you sure you're up for this?
不,杰拉尔德。我他妈一点都没准备好。 No, Gerald. I'm
definitely fucking not up for this.
Alex.
听。我们得找到那段录音。
Listen. We need to find that recording.
没有这个...他们就不能起诉。 Without that,
they-- they can't bring charges.
你记得在哪吗?
Do you remember where it is?
…我一直在努力回忆。
I-- I've been trying to remember.
好吧。
Okay.
我不能。
I can't.
丢了。
It's lost.
…我曾经做过笔记。在这里。
I-- I used to make notes. Here.
-嗯嗯。-没有笔记了。
- Mm-hm. - There's no more notes.
我很抱歉。真的。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry. Really. I'm sorry.
听。没有录音，就不能起诉西尔曼。
Listen. Without that recording,
there's no case against Sealman.
我和任何人都无能为力。 And there's nothing
that I or anybody can do about it.
你明白吗?
Do you understand that?
我需要你记起来。
I need you to remember.
迈尔斯博士。我有令状…我知道，我们接到电话说你要来。
Dr. Myers. I have a writ--
I know, we got a call you were coming.
没有酒精棉签吗?
No alcohol swab?
嘿,举起。
Hey, hold up.
你的SAC说他不能通过。
Your SAC said, he doesn't go through.
-他是我们的人。-做不到。
- He's with us. - Can't do it.
他让你直接进去。
He said for you to head right in.
没事的,男人。只是照顾。
It's okay, man. Just take care.
他抓了个人质。
He's got a hostage.
这真是一团糟，塞拉。
This is a fucking mess, Serra.
他唯一的要求就是和你谈谈。
His only demand...
is to talk to you.
嘿。
Hey.
看你的屁股。
Watch your ass.
他们出来了。
Man on radio: They're coming out.
停火。
Hold fire.
迈尔斯。
That's Myers.
二号狙击手，你能射中右边的目标吗? Sniper two, do you
have a shot on the subject on the right?
是的。
Man on radio: Affirmative.
塞拉探员,情况如何?
Man on radio: Agent Serra, status?
你杀了人质。退后！ You killed the hostage.
Stand down. Stand down!
听我说，塞拉探员，战术上…他们派那个人来杀我。
Listen to me, Agent Serra, tactical--
They sent that man to kill me.
他从警察身边走过。
He walked right past the cops.
整个游戏都是那个婊子的。
That bitch owns the whole game.
联邦调查局不是她的
She doesn't own the FBI.
-你确定吗?-听我说。
- Are you sure about that? - Listen to me.
也许他们也会杀了你。只是为了埋葬这个。
Maybe they'll kill you, too. Just to...
Just to b-- b-- bury this.
是的,也许吧。亚历克斯。听……贝里。拼写是B-E-R-Y。
Yeah, maybe. Alex. Listen--
Bery. That's spelled B-E-R-Y.
——没有。亚历克斯。——对吗?是的。是的。贝里。
- No. Alex. - Right? Yes. Yes. Bery.
B-E-R-Y。
B-E-R-Y.
你说正义无法保证。
You said justice can't be guaranteed.
不。
No.
这是我们欠那个孩子的，文森特。
We owe it to that child, Vincent.
亚历克斯。
Alex.
亚历克斯!亚历克斯!
Alex! Alex!
他们不让雨果进大楼。
They won't let Hugo in the building.
天啊，我打赌努斯鲍姆会把他驱逐出境。
God, I bet Nussbaum deports him.
是的。没有什么会让我感到惊讶。
Yeah. Nothing would surprise me.
他们要把你送到哪里?
Where are they sending you?
针对儿童的犯罪。
Crimes against Children.
——你呢?——未赋值的。
- You? - Unassigned.
文森特，你的初衷是好的。
Vincent, your heart was in the right place.
他他妈的记得。
He fucking remembered.
他他妈的记得!
He fucking remembered!
你让我别无选择。
You've left me no choice.
我不会被排除在外。
I won't be cut out.
听着，没必要搞得这么难看。
Look, this doesn't have to be ugly.
勒索已经很丑陋了。
Blackmail is already ugly.
——听着,所有…-范·坎普先生!
-Look, all-- -Mr. Van Camp!
我们不是在谈判。
We are not negotiating.
你已经越过了那条没有回头路的线。 You've crossed the
line from which there is no return.
就是这样。
That's it.
这是不够的。
It's not enough.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
亚历克斯·刘易斯死了。
Well, Alex Lewis is dead.
没有他，我就没有证据。
Without him, I don't have corroboration.
你说过，如果我把录音给你…不，不，不。录音是个威胁。是的。
You said, if I bring you this recording--
No, no, no, no. The
recording is a threat. Yes.
没有杀手，这还不够。
Without the hitman, it's not enough.
拜托，伙计，这是个案子。
Come on, man, this is a case.
这案子我赢不了。
It's not a case I can win.
我很抱歉，文森特。
I'm very sorry, Vincent.
你在开玩笑吗?
You're kidding me?
听着，当你面对那么多钱的时候，即使我让她把枪交给艾丽克丝，付钱给他，她可能还是会赢。
Look,
even if I had her handing the gun to Alex
when you're dealing with
that kind of money,</font></font>
and paying him, she'd probably still win.
好吧。好吧。
Okay. Okay.
你越早意识到这点越好。 Yeah, the sooner
you realize that, the better.
听着，你告诉我。
Listen, you tell me something.
Beatriz莱昂。
Beatriz Leon.
她对你来说意味着什么?
What does she mean to you, huh?
只是个可能会死的墨西哥小混混?
Just some lowlife Mexican kid,
不，一点也不。
who's probably gonna die anyway?
兰迪·西尔曼会把孩子们从他的拘留所带走然后把他们当做他的性玩具。
No, not at all.
Randy Sealman would take children
out of his Detention Centre
问题是，我们无法证明。
and use them as his fucking sex toys.
你知道发生了什么。我们都知道发生了什么。
Problem is, we can't prove it.
You know what's going on. We
all know what's going on.
Serra!
你他妈就是个懦夫。
You're nothing but a fucking coward.
好了，够了，塞拉!
Okay, that's it, Serra!
很多人，包括我自己，都受够了! A lot of people,
myself included, are fed up!
是的。
Yeah.
该走了，塞拉。
Time to take a leave, Serra.
长话短说。
Make it a long one.
然后我们重新评估。
And then let's re-evaluate.
乐意之至。
With pleasure.
——哟。-嗨。
- Yo. - Hey.
我们应该庆祝你被停职。
We should celebrate your suspension.
我还没准备好。
I'm not really up for it.
我没问，笨蛋。
I wasn't asking, dipshit.
快他妈的穿上衣服。
Get some fucking clothes on.
你什么时候这么爱交际了?
Since when have you been so social?
我在努力改过自新。
I'm trying to turn over a new leaf.
我是说，你不可能永远都是混蛋，对吧? I mean, you can't
be an asshole forever, right?
我不知道。
I don't know.
——嘿!-不不不。
- Hey! - No, no, no.
我明天就完蛋了。
Anymore and I'm fucking toast tomorrow.
别像个娘们儿。
Don't be a pussy.
你又不是有工作。
It's not like you've got a job.
我很好。
I'm good.
好吧。
Alright.
哦,该死。我忘带钱包了。
Oh, shit. I spaced my wallet.
对不起。我欠你。
Sorry. I'll owe you.
混蛋。
Asshole.
Sol?
几小时前在家里被杀。 Man on TV: ...murdered
just hours ago at her home.
据埃尔帕索警察局发言人称，目前没有嫌疑人，也没有目击者。 According to
an El Paso Police Department spokesmen,
there are presently no
suspects and no witnesses.
细节目前还不清楚。埃尔帕索警方… Details are sketchy
at this point. El Paso Police only...
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
你刚给了我不在场证明吗?
Did you just give me an alibi?
阿门。
Amen.